# **IHDA ANWARI**

087719873642 | ihdaanwari5@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ihda-anwari | ihda06.github.io/

Jln. Siliwangi Gang Bakri

I am a digital business student who has an interest in front-end developers, graphic designers, and UI/UX designers. I am capable of designing UI Websites with ReactJs and Laravel, I have experienced building websites as a full stack with laravel. I am also familiar with design tools like Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Figma, Canva, and CorelDraw

# Work Experiences

AVPN Asia - Singapore May 2022 - Aug 2022

Frontend Intern

- · Designing UI and UX for the website project with Figma
- Creating a mockup prototype for the website project with ReactJs
- · Handle data mockup with nocode App Airtable

#### Univesitas Padjadjaran - Sumedang, Indonesia

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Teaching Assistant Web Development

- Teaching 2 classes that consists of >40 students to practice web development coding using HTML, CSS, PHP, and mySQL with Visual Studio Code and Sublime Text.
- · Arranging 2 classes schedule.
- Creating >10 quizzes.

## BEM Kema Unpad - Sumedang, Indonesia

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Project Lead

• Creating a website as a full-stack developer with Laravel that will be used by students that want to participate in a national competition called PKM a kind of business idea competition

#### Sekolah.mu - Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

Frontend Intern

- Designing 3 website components for front end design system at Sekolah.mu including implementing to storybook and creating the unit test on each component
- Achieve 95% average unit test for each component
- · Participating to improve feature on payment page

#### Antares by Telkom - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - Jun 2023

Developer Intern

- Develop 5 simple sub menus for application needs such as create the database, create API, and front-end view
- Fix and improve more than 10 sub menu

## **Education Level**

### Padjadjaran University - Sumedang, Indonesia

Aug 2019 - Jun 2023

Bachelor Degree in Digital Business, 3.84/4.00

- · Received an A grade in UI/UX, Web Development, Web & Mobile Technology courses
- Received an A grade in Business Intelligence, Digital Marketing, and Social Media Management

#### Organisational Experience

## Bem Kema Unpad - Sumedang, Indonesia

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Staff Academic and Inovation Department

- Manage and organize all social media posts including designing, publishing and draftingCreating website for PKM
- · Become the best staff in the second period

## Hima Bisnis Digital - Sumedang, Indonesia

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Assistant Manager Creative Media

· Manage and organize all social media posts including designing, publishing and drafting

# Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Course (2022): Taking the Front-End Track at Generasi Gigih Program from Yayasan Anak Bangsa Bisa & GoTo
- Tech Hard Skills: Develop user interface website with ReactJs, Develop fullstack website with Laravel, Develop Mobile Interface with

## Flutter

- Business Hard Skills: Creating a dashboard with Tableau, creating associative analysis for recommendation with KNIME, familiar with social media tools analytics
- Design Hard Skills: Familiar with design tools like Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Coreldraw, Canva
- Language Skills: Bahasa Native
- Language Skills: English Proficient